a
soldier drove
Roman
A
a dead man's
into
spear
to be sure He
side
gone.
was
he
idea
He had no
God
sentence
was finishing a
earlier.
centuries
five
wrote
Zechariah,
In
in the first
speaks
God
His
the day
person about
someone
pierce
people would
staggering:
something
and says
me
look upon
"...they shall
pierced,
they have
whom
for
mourn
and they shall
him,
for his
mourneth
as one
son..."
only
it twice.
Read
Me
pierced
God says they
then,
for Him.
mourn
somehow
man is
The pierced
Himself
God
Son.
God's own
cross,
At the
the spear go
watched
John
in,
for that exact
reached
and
verse:
on him
look
"They shall
pierced."
they
whom
mercy:
the
And here is
answers
they pierced
God
the
with wrath,
not
out
poured
but with grace
finally
they
so that when
look,
just see what
don't
they
did.
mourn,
They
forgiven.
and they are
cross
that
The man on
God
victim
was not a
to save.
failed
God,
He was
for you.
pierced
at Him
Look
live.
and